(Sheldon:)...and we transplanted a dog's head
in its place...
...would that be "problem solved"?
(Leonard:)If it were your head, it would be.
(Penny:)Sheldon, I am really, really sorry,
but it's only for a week.
(Penny:)Can't you be a little bit flexible?
(Howard:)Yeah, sorry,
I didn't really think that through.
(Sheldon:)You claim it's going to be a week.
I have no faith in your cleaner.
- Why not?
- Did you notice the sign on his counter?
(Sheldon:)He's not a full-time dry cleaner.
(Sheldon:)He also makes keys.
(Leonard:)Oh, for God's sake, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Focus is important.
(Sheldon:)Was Michael DeBakey a wedding
planner in between heart transplants?
(Sheldon:)Did Alexander Fleming
moonlight as a hair dresser?
(Sheldon:)Thanks for discovering penicillin.
Now how about we try a bouffant?
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
(Howard(after his phone rings):)Oh, looks like
I'm gonna have sex tonight.
HOWARD: Hey, baby.
- His right hand is calling him?
(Leonard:)No, it's Leslie Winkle. It's a long story.